It will take you to the edge of suspense.
Narrow Margin is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Peter Hyams.
District Attorney attempts to take an unwilling murder witness back to
the United States to testify against a top-level mob boss.
Frantically attempting to escape two deadly hitmen sent to silence her, they board a
Vancouver-bound train only to discover that the killers are onboard with them.
For the next 20 hours, as the train hurls through the beautiful but isolated Canadian wilderness, a deadly game of
cat and mouse ensues in which their ability to tell friend from foe is a matter of life and death.
Robert Caulfield, played by Gene Hackman.
Carol Hunnicut, played by Anne Archer.
Nelson, played by James B. Sikking.
Leo Watts, played by Harris Yulin.
Michael Tarlow, played by J. T. Walsh.
Sergeant Dominick Benti, played by M. Emmet Walsh.
Narrow Margin is a 1990 American neo-noir action thriller
film written and directed by Peter Hyams.
It stars Gene Hackman and Anne Archer, with James B.
Sikking, Nigel Bennett, Harris Yulin and J.
Walsh in supporting roles.
It was released in the United States by TriStar Pictures on September 21, 1990.
Based on the 1952 film The Narrow Margin, it is the first of two RKO
reimaginings by Hyams, the other being 2009's Beyond a Reasonable Doubt.
The film keeps the same general story, and follows Los Angeles deputy district attorney Robert Caulfield who
attempts to keep murder witness Carol Hunnicut safe from hitmen while traveling on a train.
However, it changes the moral alignment of some characters, and the
setting from the Super Chief route to the Canadian Rockies.
The film explores themes of witness protection, night train, jump from train.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.